(Howard:)So, Dr. Hofstadter...
(Howard:)...Leonard rarely talks about his
incredibly successful brother and sister.
- Please don't go there, Howard.
- You know, I understand...
(Howard:)...that unlike Leonard,
they're at the top of their respective fields.
(Leonard:)Boy, you suck.
(Beverley:)Leonard's younger brother, Michael,
is a tenured law professor at Harvard...
(Beverley:)...and his sister just successfully grew
a human pancreas in an adolescent gibbon.
(Howard:)So she's close to curing diabetes?
(Beverley:)Why else would you grow
a pancreas in a teenaged gibbon?
(Howard:)Wow, you must be very proud.
(Beverley:)Why? They're not my accomplishments.
(Beverley:)I have to urinate.
- Why are you doing this?
- You know the rules.
(Howard:)You brought your mom to work.
You must suffer.
[HOWARD CHUCKLES]
(Sheldon:)Leonard, I had no idea your siblings
were so much more successful than you.
[RAJESH CHUCKLES]
(Raj:)Yeah, you're like the Jar Jar Binks
of the Hofstadter family.